cumbrowski.com 2018-06-29

# Cumbrowski.com Privacy Policy - Your Privacy is Important

**Cumbrowski.com Privacy Policy**

**DO NOT USE THIS SITE IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

I do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties without your explicit permission. Any personal data collected by me will be used only by me. Any future request for permission to release customer (your) information to 3rd parties will be done clearly, directly and personaly ONLY and not via hidden or "small print" forms. Please note, that I am required to provide information to international, federal or california law enforcement agencies if they make an legal and official request which I can not deny by law.

**Collection of Non-PII (Non Personally Identifiable Information)**  
I currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize my Internet Operations and communications. I use the services of marketing companies to help me measure the effectiveness of advertisments and promotions and how visitors use the site. To do this, I use Action Tags and cookies provided by the marketing companies on this site. The information I collect help me learn things like what kinds of visitors the site attracts, which of my provided resources most interest my Visitors, and what kinds of content my visitors like to see. 

**Public Disclosure of Cumbrowski.com Analytics Data**  
One Service I use is SiteMeter. SiteMeter allows me to share publically the information that are tracked and some statistics that are probably not just interesting for me. [Check them out](http://www.sitemeter.com/?a=stats&s=s29cumbrowski).

Additional Tracking Services used are Google Analytics, MyWebLog, HitTail, CrazyEgg and some in-house developed tracking. I also plugin other Services from time to time for testing and research purposes. Looking for a Tracking and Web Analytics solution for yourself? [Clicktracks](http://www.cumbrowski.com/CarstenC/Web-Analytics-Software.asp) is a good and professional solution. Also check my [Web Analytics Resources](http://www.cumbrowski.com/CarstenC/internetmarketing_webanalytics.asp). 

Although the marketing companies logs the information coming from me site on my behalf, I control to a certain extend how that data may and may not be used.

**Email Opt-In and Opt-Out**  
I may send you newsletters and promotional offers via-email when you use the Blog Feed subscription form on this Website.

The Subscription covers my posts at ReveNews.com and SearchEngineJournal.com and Cumbrowski.com News.

If you do not wish to continue to receive any of this information open the original subscription confirmation email or wait until you receive another e-mail which contains the instruction how to unsubscribe and be removed from my mailing list.

**Use of Cookies**  
This site uses cookies to personalize and improve your experience. It also uses Cookies for Tracking and Statistical purposes. These cookies do not contain any confidential or personal information.

**Security**  
I use industry-standard methods to protect your information from unauthorized access. Among other techniques, I store such information on a computer behind our "firewall" in a secure location, and restrict the number of employees internally who can access such data. Any data is stored in a password-protected server. Please be aware, of course, that there is no such thing as perfect security - on or off the Internet.

**Sites linked to from Cumbrowski.com**  
Please keep security in mind as you reach other websites through links from Cumbrowski.com. Each separate company has its own privacy policies and practices and may market to you accordingly. Although I choose the Sites I am referring to carefully, I can make no representations concerning privacy and security on those sites.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any concerns or questions with respect to my Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact me](http://www.cumbrowski.com/contact.asp).

 **By using this site, you are agreeing to the conditions of this Privacy Policy.**

If I decide to change my Privacy Policy in whole or in part it will be posted on the site. Please check this page periodically for changes.
